







Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

?6 years of experience as System Analyst, Devops Engineer and Linux Admin.

?Working experience on pipeline and mutlibranch pipeline for our services in development, staging, and pre-production environment by using the integrated Tools Jenkins.

?Administrated and Implemented CI tools Jenkins for automated builds .

?Jenkins Master and Slave setup.

?Proficient in using Configuration Management tools such as Ansible on Linux machines. Created many customized modules Playbooks for configuring applications on the client nodes.

?Strong ability to troubleshoot any issues generated while building, deploying and in production support and schedule and run tasks in background using Crontab.

?Closely worked with development, QA and other teams to ensure automated test efforts are tightly integrated with the build system and in fixing the error while doing the deployment and building.

?Managed GIT as Source Control Systems.

Work Experience

- UST Global as System Analyst Mar 2020 to Till Date
- UST Global as System Analyst Mar 2020 to Dec 2020
- Fabex Tech Solutions pvt ltd as Devops Engineer Jan 2017 to Mar 2020
- Idealsource Technologies pvt. ltd. as Linux System Administrator Oct 2014 to Dec 2016

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2013

^ Back to Top

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
WINDOWS, LINUX		
GIT		
Tomcat		
MAVEN		
Docker, Kubernetes		
Jenkins		
Ansible		
AMAZON Web Services		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English		✓	✓	✓
Hindi		✓	✓	✓
Odia		✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.